Antonio Priego Raya

Game Developer

After two years of training and developing video game projects in my spare time; I have decided to follow my heart and take the leap into the videogame industry as creating games satisfies me like nothing else.

antoniopriego.github.io/portfolio github.com/AntonioPriego linkedin.com/in/antonio-priego-raya

antoniopriego98@outlook.com

Cordoba, Andalusia, Spain

+34 643345932

EXPERIENCE

NTT Data, Remote

Mid Salesforce Developer

November 2023 - Present

- I am promoted to mid developer, which is a double jump in the internal hierarchy of the company because they are very satisfied with my work.
- The development of the project at Damm came to an end with very satisfactory results and a team of colleagues that we all wanted to continue to be part of.
- I am teaming up with the Salesforce support team in anticipation of a new project.

NTT Data, Remote

Junior Salesforce Developer

November 2022 - November 2023

- First contact with labour world.
- I trained by obtaining official Salesforce certifications while working on a Telefónica project.
- My first project as lead developer at Damm.

GAMEDEV PROJECTS HIGHLIGHTED

Multiplayer RPG Waves Survival

Developed with Unreal Engine & C++

May 2023 - October 2023

- Multiplayer / Replication, Component based actors, Custom Gameplay Ability System, Mid-Complex animations system, Gameplay tags usage, Mid-Complex Behavior Trees, Navigation System, Environment Query System, BT Tasks, Mid-Complex UI UMG Widgets, Shooter & Abilities system, Materials focused on gameplay, Deep engine architecture knowledge, Basic Menus, Basic Save System, Efficient Asset Management, etc.
- Developed while doing guided learning with Tom Looman's course.

Coffee Shop OpenGL scene

Developed with OpenGL, Glut & C++

September 2019 - January 2020

• Graphics, lighting, texturing and hierarchical animated models.

SKILLS

Unreal Engine Blueprints

C++

Git | Github

GDD

Linux

Python

Java

C#

LANGUAGES

- English | B2 CEFR | C1 NTT Data
- Spanish | Native

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

Agile Development Course By Juan Julián Merelo (UGR proffesor)

English CEFR B2 Trinity

Professional Game Development in C++ and Unreal Engine

EDUCATION

Computer engineering

Expertise in hardware 2017-2022

University of Granada

• **Awards:** Honours in my final degree project

Baccalaureate

2015-2017

IES Inca Garcilaso, Spain